import { Question } from '@/src/types/questions'

const hiraganaYouon: Question[] = [
  {
    "question": "What is the hiragana for \"kya\"?",
    "options": [
      "ぎゃ",
      "しゅ",
      "きゃ",
      "ぎゅ"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "きゃ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the hiragana for \"kyu\"?",
    "options": [
      "びょ",
      "びゃ",
      "ぎょ",
      "きゅ"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "きゅ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the hiragana for \"kyo\"?",
    "options": [
      "ぎょ",
      "ひょ",
      "ちょ",
      "きょ"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "きょ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the hiragana for \"gya\"?",
    "options": [
      "きゅ",
      "きょ",
      "ぴゃ",
      "ぎゃ"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "ぎゃ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the hiragana for \"gyu\"?",
    "options": [
      "ぎゅ",
      "みゅ",
      "ひゅ",
      "しゃ"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "ぎゅ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the hiragana for \"gyo\"?",
    "options": [
      "ぎょ",
      "りょ",
      "きゅ",
      "びゅ"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "ぎょ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the hiragana for \"sha\"?",
    "options": [
      "じゅ",
      "みょ",
      "りょ",
      "しゃ"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "しゃ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the hiragana for \"shu\"?",
    "options": [
      "しゅ",
      "びょ",
      "きゃ",
      "きゅ"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "しゅ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the hiragana for \"sho\"?",
    "options": [
      "りゃ",
      "りゅ",
      "しょ",
      "ちゃ"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "しょ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the hiragana for \"ja\"?",
    "options": [
      "きゅ",
      "ぴゅ",
      "しゃ",
      "じゃ"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "じゃ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the hiragana for \"ju\"?",
    "options": [
      "にゃ",
      "じゅ",
      "ひょ",
      "ひゃ"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "じゅ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the hiragana for \"jo\"?",
    "options": [
      "ちゃ",
      "にゃ",
      "ぎゅ",
      "じょ"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "じょ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the hiragana for \"cha\"?",
    "options": [
      "ぎょ",
      "ちゃ",
      "にゃ",
      "ぴゃ"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "ちゃ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the hiragana for \"chu\"?",
    "options": [
      "ちゅ",
      "しょ",
      "じゅ",
      "ぎゃ"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "ちゅ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the hiragana for \"cho\"?",
    "options": [
      "りゅ",
      "じゅ",
      "ちょ",
      "にょ"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "ちょ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the hiragana for \"nya\"?",
    "options": [
      "にゃ",
      "ちょ",
      "みょ",
      "ちゅ"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "にゃ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the hiragana for \"nyu\"?",
    "options": [
      "りゃ",
      "きゃ",
      "にゅ",
      "しゅ"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "にゅ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the hiragana for \"nyo\"?",
    "options": [
      "びょ",
      "にょ",
      "ひゅ",
      "しゅ"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "にょ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the hiragana for \"hya\"?",
    "options": [
      "ぎゅ",
      "ひゅ",
      "みゃ",
      "ひゃ"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "ひゃ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the hiragana for \"hyu\"?",
    "options": [
      "ひゅ",
      "きゃ",
      "ぴゅ",
      "ひょ"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "ひゅ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the hiragana for \"hyo\"?",
    "options": [
      "ひょ",
      "りょ",
      "みゅ",
      "みゃ"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "ひょ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the hiragana for \"bya\"?",
    "options": [
      "きょ",
      "ちゃ",
      "びゃ",
      "ちゅ"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "びゃ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the hiragana for \"byu\"?",
    "options": [
      "みょ",
      "しゃ",
      "にゅ",
      "びゅ"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "びゅ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the hiragana for \"byo\"?",
    "options": [
      "ひょ",
      "しゃ",
      "にゅ",
      "びょ"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "びょ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the hiragana for \"pya\"?",
    "options": [
      "にょ",
      "ぴゃ",
      "ちゃ",
      "ぎゃ"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "ぴゃ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the hiragana for \"pyu\"?",
    "options": [
      "きょ",
      "みゅ",
      "ぴゅ",
      "しゃ"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "ぴゅ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the hiragana for \"pyo\"?",
    "options": [
      "ぎゃ",
      "ぴょ",
      "ぴゃ",
      "きょ"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "ぴょ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the hiragana for \"mya\"?",
    "options": [
      "みゃ",
      "りゃ",
      "ぎゅ",
      "しゃ"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "みゃ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the hiragana for \"myu\"?",
    "options": [
      "しゅ",
      "ぴゃ",
      "みゅ",
      "びゃ"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "みゅ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the hiragana for \"myo\"?",
    "options": [
      "ぎゃ",
      "ぎょ",
      "みょ",
      "ぴょ"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "みょ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the hiragana for \"rya\"?",
    "options": [
      "じゃ",
      "びゃ",
      "りゃ",
      "きゃ"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "りゃ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the hiragana for \"ryu\"?",
    "options": [
      "しょ",
      "にゃ",
      "りゅ",
      "みゅ"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "りゅ"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the hiragana for \"ryo\"?",
    "options": [
      "きゅ",
      "りょ",
      "しゅ",
      "ぎゃ"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "りょ"
  }
]

export default hiraganaYouon;